{
    "id": "64666a9c432e4557999a4398b9f19b5e",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Humpty Dumpty sat ........................ a wall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f89fec878c294996832a7f1f5a7cd28f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The lion and the unicorn fought ........................... the crown.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6aaf58cbe7a545289d000dcbaf0593d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Little Jack Horner sat ...................... a corner.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "04b15bbae41d48c59bf8d2acb2c2f223"
        },
        {
            "question": "Wee Willie Winkie runs ....................... the town.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "over",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "60c1eef6db0d406ab055d6ba0e82030d"
        },
        {
            "question": "A fair little girl sat ....................... a tree.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "below",
                "under",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b51e22779f0e4304a8d99aede433cb00"
        },
        {
            "question": "I bring fresh showers for the thirsty flowers .......................... the seas and the streams.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "from",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c868e385aa1042ac9801641f8582a153"
        },
        {
            "question": "She laid her arms .......................... her breast.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "across",
                "above"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "46cbb06b4335460188fe131f45e84788"
        },
        {
            "question": "I tried to reason him ............................. his fears.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "out of",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8fc31f7e83fe4153b93df33a8c2f8312"
        },
        {
            "question": "He swore ...................... the nine Gods.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "by",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "09cb87f3f56b40709050fd1d541bf598"
        },
        {
            "question": "One day the boy took his breakfast and ate it by a purling brook which ran ......................... his motherâ€™s orchard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "through",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e4c54574b29445549ed0229a3838a64c"
        },
        {
            "question": "One crowded hour of glorious life is worth an age ....................... a name.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "without",
                "against",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c895fbc9489641ef9ec32ad96fb4274d"
        }
    ]
}